

Lead Developer seeking roles in Project Management, Software Development, Software Testing, Automation Testing, Manual Testing, Defect Management, Test Planning, Requirement Analysis, Risk Management, Java script,jQuery,MySQL



Current Designation: Lead Total Experience: 12 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Hamad Bin Khalifa University Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: DOHA Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Team Leading, Drupal, Solution Architecture, Client Handling, Web

Development, PHP

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science 12+ years of experience in web application including 10+ years in Drupal Working as a Lead developer in HBKU with InsideJob Management UK Limited Developed cross-platform applications with Drupal, WordPress, PHP, ReactJS.

Developed solutions in various domains like University, Travel, Social network, Departmental store, etc

Work Experience

Hamad Bin Khalifa University as Lead

Aug 2017 to Till Date

HBKU is public university in Doha, Qatar. Working as Lead developer to providing solution of CMS (Content Management System) in Drupal 7, Drupal 8 and WP. Leading Team, Server Management, CMS Solutions approach and development are my core responsibility here.

Happiest Minds Technologies as Senior Software Engineer Aug 2012 to Aug 2017

Happiest Minds Technologies is a digital transformation, infrastructure, security, and product engineering services. company. I got a change to work on Drupal, PHP and ReactJS

Ballistic Learning Pvt. Ltd as Software Engineer Jan 2009 to Aug 2012

Ballistic Learning focus solution provide for LMS (Learning Management System). I got change to work on Moodle, Drupal, Core PHP projects.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Uttar Pradesh Technical University (UPTU) in 2008

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
MySQL, Javascript, HTML, CSS	
PHP	
Drupal 7, Drupal 8	
PIMCore, Moodle	
ReactJs, GatsbyJs	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Projects

Project Title: Hamad Bin Khalifa University Qatar

Client: Qatar Foundation

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Aug 2017 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Hamad Bin Khalifa University, is a public university located within Education City in Doha, the capital city of

Qatar. Hamad Bin Khalifa University, a member of Qatar Foundation for Education

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time